<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MealPrep</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">BLD_Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bmi_screen_">BMI_Activity</string>
    <string name="Testing_HelloWorld">Hello World Its Chef-D\'s Meal Prep!</string>
    <string name="OverHeadMainScreenText">Findr</string>
    <string name="MainTopButton">Breakfast</string>
    <string name="MainMiddleButton">lunch</string>
    <string name="MainBottomButton">Dinner</string>
    <string name="title_activity_breakfast">Breakfast_Activity</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="protein">protein</string>
    <string name="Carbohydrates">Carbohydrates</string>
    <string name="Vegetables">Vegetables/Fruit</string>
    <string name="Favorite">Favorite</string>
    <string name="title_activity_vegetables_">Vegetables_Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_protein_">Vegetables_Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_carbs_">Vegetables_Activity</string>
    <string name="recipe_v_textview">recipe sentence</string>
    <string name="recipe_p_textview">recipe sentence</string>
    <string name="recipe_c_textview">recipe sentence</string>
    <string name="banana_pancakes">Banana Pancakes</string>
    <string name="banana_pancakes_proteins">Ingredients: Two Eggs \n\n Instructions: Two Eggs, In a pan, crack two eggs and scramble them until fluffy. Add to dish when finished.</string>
    <string name="banana_pancakes_veg_fruits">Ingredients: Bananas \n\n Instructions: Peel banana, then cut them 1/2inch slices, then add to dish. </string>
    <string name="banana_pancakes_carbs">Ingredients: 1 cup all-purpose flour, 1 tablespoon white sugar, 2 teaspoons baking powder, 1/4 teaspoon salt, 1 egg, beaten, 1 cup milk, 2 tablespoons vegetable oil, 2 ripe bananas, mashed. \n \nInstructions: Combine flour, white sugar, baking powder and salt. In a separate bowl, mix together egg, milk, vegetable oil and bananas.Stir flour mixture into banana mixture; batter will be slightly lumpy. Heat a lightly oiled griddle or frying pan over medium high heat. Pour or scoop the batter onto the griddle, using approximately 1/4 cup for each pancake. Cook until pancakes are golden brown on both sides; serve hot.</string>
    <string name="bmi_calculator">BMI Calculator</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">AboutActivity</string>
    <string name="about_text">This company was founded in 2016 at some alloted time.
                              The reason im writing this much is so that i can see if the text
                              view and scroll view are working together and that the scroll view
                              is able to scroll. So what im going to do now is copy and pase what
                              i just wrote. Please disregard the following text because you have
                              already read it.This company was founded in 2016 at some alloted
                               time. The reason im writing this much is so that i can see if the
                               text view and scroll view are working together and that the scroll
                               view is able to scroll. So what im going to do now is copy and pase
                               what i just wrote. Please disregard the following text because you
                                have already read it.This company was founded in 2016 at some
                               alloted time. The reason im writing this much is so that i can see
                               if the text view and scroll view are working together and that the
                               scroll view is able to scroll. So what im going to do now is copy
                               and pase what i just wrote. Please disregard the following text
                               because you have already read it. This company was founded in 2016 at
                               some alloted time. The reason im writing this
                            much is so that i can see if the text view and scroll
                            view are working together and that the scroll view is able
                            to scroll. So what im going to do now is copy and pase what i
                            just wrote. Please disregard the following text because you have
                            already read it.This company was founded in 2016 at some alloted time.
                            The reason im writing this much is so that i can see if the text view
                            and scroll view are working together and that the scroll view is able
                            to scroll. So what im going to do now is copy and pase what i just wrote.
                            Please disregard the following text because you have already read it.This
                            company was founded in 2016 at some alloted time. The reason im writing
                            this much is so that i can see if the text view and scroll view are
                            working together and that the scroll view is able to scroll.</string>
    <string name="overnight_oats">Peanut Butter Banana Overnight Oats</string>
    <string name="seed_pudding">Creamy Blueberry Chia Seed Pudding</string>
    <string name="yogurt_granola">Super Simple Yogurt and Granola Parfaits</string>
    <string name="Kale_hash">Sweet Potato Kale Hash</string>
    <string name="breakfast_burritos">Breakfast Burritos</string>
    <string name="title_activity_calories">CaloriesActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_calorie_view">CalorieViewActivity</string>
    <string name="viewcalviewText">Go to Food Calorie List</string>
    <string name="textbmrdescription">Basal metabolic rate (BMR), is the amount of energy expressed in calories that a person needs to keep the body functioning at rest. This amount of calories is HIGHLY recommended.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_aboutme">aboutme</string>
    <string name="calorie_counter_title">Calorie Counter</string>
    <string name="about_me_title">Aboutme</string>

</resources>
